dealdoodle.co.uk 2017-02-03

# Privacy Policy - DealDoodle UK

## Privacy Policy

last update: 17-07-2015

### The short version

We at DealDoodle will only use any personal information we collect to help us provide you with a better service. We will never sell, distribute or lease your personal information. Just bear in mind that our privacy policy only covers the data that we collect from DealDoodle. Once you click to another site from ours you are no longer in our jurisdiction. 

### The long version

This privacy policy sets out how DealDoodle.co.uk uses and protects any information that you give DealDoodle.co.uk when you use this website. 

DealDoodle.co.uk is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. DealDoodle.co.uk may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. 

You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1 Jan 2015. 

We may collect information such as name, job title, contact information including an email address, referrer URL, demographic information (ie postcode, preferences and interests) and information relevant to customer surveys & offers. This information enables us to provide you with a better service as well as understanding your needs better. The reason is that it enables internal record keeping, may also enable us to customise our website according to your interests and from time to time we may use this information to contact you for research purposes. 

#### Our use of cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. 

Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

#### Links to other websites

Our website will contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

#### Controlling your personal information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law.
